ListView是把所有可见条目显示在一个view上  可见条目数量取决于
ListView starts by requesting a view for every visible item, however many you
手机屏幕的大小  与此同时  它同时会在上下两头初始化一对条目
can fit onto the screen. It'll also create a couple in either direction to make
以确保新的视图创建并填充的时候  滑动起来的时候不会卡顿
sure we can scroll without seeing a flicker as a new view is created and
然后他就很快的把新条目创建了  然后下一行就为用户
populated. Then it creates new items just in time. So it's next in line to
呈现了  也就是说  如果用户木有滚动到列表的最下面
be visible to the user. So if the user never scrolls to the bottom of the list,
那ListView也就永远不会从接口请求数据
the ListView will never request that view from the adapter. But this is really
这确实只是一个折中的办法  你想想看  如果用户一直在滑动屏幕
just a half measure. As you can see, if the user keeps scrolling, we could
我们只是一味的在添加新的视图  即使它们从顶部已经消失了
potentially just keep adding new views, even if they disappear off the top of
最终结果是它们一直在内存中占着资源
the screen. Eventually that's going to lead to the same impact in memory use and
那这就跟我们初始化的时候就把它们全部加载到内存里一模一样了
performance as if we had just created all of these views directly at
那么解决方案就是  自动把所有划出屏幕的视图全部回收
the beginning. The solution is recycling each view as it scrolls off the screen,
当条目被滑动回屏幕的时候
allowing it to be reused when we need to show another item as it
重新启用  而不是在视图实例化的时候
moves into view at the top or bottom. So rather than having to create and
将他们全部放进内存
then hold in memory each item of the list as it comes in to view,
所以我们只需要为这些在手机屏幕里可见的条目申请内存
we only need to do the creation step for the number of visible items and
这样的话任何时候一个新的视图显示到手机上的时候
couple on either side. Then whenever a new list item comes into view,
我们只需要更新列表的数据就可以了
we just update the data displayed in one of our items in our recycle bin.
为啥要这么折腾  结果就是更少的内存占用  更顺畅的滑动体验
The result? Less memory overhead, smoother scrolling and
而且你只用做更少的视图管理工作  这种回收机制
less view management you have to do yourself. This same recycling behavior is
是由AdapterView的子类实现的  比如GridView和ListView
implemented across all AdapterView descended classes, such as GridView and
ListView, which also introduces the reason that the adapter isn't built
directly into these controls themself. By keeping them separate,
your adapter defines how to display each element of the underlying data,
while the adapter view implementation itself is responsible for
controlling how each of these elements is laid out. Be it a list or
a grid in these particular instances.